[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "CD", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 30, "question": "How on earth do you do so much?", "question_tokens": ["How", "on", "earth", "do", "you", "do", "so", "much", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 31, "answer": "Well, I just put one foot in front of the other and keep it moving.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "just", "put", "one", "foot", "in", "front", "of", "the", "other", "and", "keep", "it", "moving", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 45, "question": "Put family aside for one moment, professionally, if I could offer you the chance to just do one of those things everyday?", "question_tokens": ["Put", "family", "aside", "for", "one", "moment", ",", "professionally", ",", "if", "I", "could", "offer", "you", "the", "chance", "to", "just", "do", "one", "of", "those", "things", "everyday", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VB", "NN", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NN", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "RB", "VB", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 46, "answer": "Oh my goodness.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", "my", "goodness", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "IN", "CD", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "PRP", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 49, "question": "What do you think is the one thing you love most?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "is", "the", "one", "thing", "you", "love", "most", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBZ", "DT", "CD", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJS", "."], "aSentId": 50, "answer": "I think that's been my curse, that I can't really find that one thing that keeps me content and happy.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "'s", "been", "my", "curse", ",", "that", "I", "ca", "n't", "really", "find", "that", "one", "thing", "that", "keeps", "me", "content", "and", "happy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 59, "question": "Right, but what about professionally?", "question_tokens": ["Right", ",", "but", "what", "about", "professionally", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "CC", "WP", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 60, "answer": "Music.", "answer_tokens": ["Music", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 80, "question": "What was it like for you growing up in a single parent household?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "it", "like", "for", "you", "growing", "up", "in", "a", "single", "parent", "household", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 81, "answer": "Very hard.", "answer_tokens": ["Very", "hard", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 86, "question": "No money, really?", "question_tokens": ["No", "money", ",", "really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 87, "answer": "We didn't have a lot of money.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "did", "n't", "have", "a", "lot", "of", "money", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNPS", ",", "RB", "RB", "RBR", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 92, "question": "Is she as kick-ass as you are?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "she", "as", "kick-ass", "as", "you", "are", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 93, "answer": "MITH: Yes, probably even more so.", "answer_tokens": ["MITH", ":", "Yes", ",", "probably", "even", "more", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 96, "question": "What did she teach you, your mother, in terms of value, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "she", "teach", "you", ",", "your", "mother", ",", "in", "terms", "of", "value", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 97, "answer": "I think the endurance.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "the", "endurance", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBG", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "RB", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "RB", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 107, "question": "From your father?", "question_tokens": ["From", "your", "father", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 108, "answer": "From my father and, you know, having been raised by a young mother who was really trying to find her way as well as having a little girl by her side.", "answer_tokens": ["From", "my", "father", "and", ",", "you", "know", ",", "having", "been", "raised", "by", "a", "young", "mother", "who", "was", "really", "trying", "to", "find", "her", "way", "as", "well", "as", "having", "a", "little", "girl", "by", "her", "side", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 117, "question": "Did he get better as he got older?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "he", "get", "better", "as", "he", "got", "older", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJR", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJR", "."], "aSentId": 118, "answer": "I would say that before he passed, we had an opportunity to find common ground.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "say", "that", "before", "he", "passed", ",", "we", "had", "an", "opportunity", "to", "find", "common", "ground", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 122, "question": "Did you forgive him?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "forgive", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 123, "answer": "I forgive him now.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "forgive", "him", "now", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 130, "question": "ORGAN: What do you think you get from him in terms of your personality?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "What", "do", "you", "think", "you", "get", "from", "him", "in", "terms", "of", "your", "personality", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 131, "answer": "My creative mind.", "answer_tokens": ["My", "creative", "mind", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 137, "question": "And for your mother, I mean, what does she make of this, absurd way that your life has turned since those early days?", "question_tokens": ["And", "for", "your", "mother", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "what", "does", "she", "make", "of", "this", ",", "absurd", "way", "that", "your", "life", "has", "turned", "since", "those", "early", "days", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", ",", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 138, "answer": "I think she's amazed, you know, and it doesn't stop.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "she", "'s", "amazed", ",", "you", "know", ",", "and", "it", "does", "n't", "stop", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 139, "question": "Does she worry about you?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "she", "worry", "about", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 140, "answer": "She worries when I work too hard.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "worries", "when", "I", "work", "too", "hard", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBD", "NNP", ":", ":", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP"], "qSentId": 150, "question": "Hello?", "question_tokens": ["Hello", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 151, "answer": "NIDENTIFIED MALE: (SPEAKING FOREIGN LANGUAGE)", "answer_tokens": ["NIDENTIFIED", "MALE", ":", "(", "SPEAKING", "FOREIGN", "LANGUAGE", ")"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Morrisey"]}, "docId": "110617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 152, "question": "You sure you got the right number?", "question_tokens": ["You", "sure", "you", "got", "the", "right", "number", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 153, "answer": "I'll make this meeting with Morrisey quick.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ll", "make", "this", "meeting", "with", "Morrisey", "quick", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "VBZ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 159, "question": "Well you just make sure you keep my side of the bed warm, OK?", "question_tokens": ["Well", "you", "just", "make", "sure", "you", "keep", "my", "side", "of", "the", "bed", "warm", ",", "OK", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "JJ", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBN", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 160, "answer": "No, what's mine is yours.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "what", "'s", "mine", "is", "yours", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 162, "question": "I mean, it all happens on that show, doesn't it?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "it", "all", "happens", "on", "that", "show", ",", "does", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 163, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":"], "qSentId": 168, "question": "What does the other man in your life, the one sitting opposite you right now, what does he make of all that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "does", "the", "other", "man", "in", "your", "life", ",", "the", "one", "sitting", "opposite", "you", "right", "now", ",", "what", "does", "he", "make", "of", "all", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "DT", "CD", "VBG", "JJ", "PRP", "RB", "RB", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 169, "answer": "He --", "answer_tokens": ["He", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ":"], "qSentId": 177, "question": "He produces it with you, right?", "question_tokens": ["He", "produces", "it", "with", "you", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 178, "answer": "Yes, he does and I think it --", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "he", "does", "and", "I", "think", "it", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 192, "question": "Can you watch him do it?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "watch", "him", "do", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 193, "answer": "I can.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "can", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 203, "question": "Are you going to ask me when we come back?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "going", "to", "ask", "me", "when", "we", "come", "back", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 204, "answer": "When we come back.", "answer_tokens": ["When", "we", "come", "back", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "POS", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 211, "question": "What do you think of that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "of", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 212, "answer": "I would say that's pretty much on the nose.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "say", "that", "'s", "pretty", "much", "on", "the", "nose", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 215, "question": "Much more than people might think?", "question_tokens": ["Much", "more", "than", "people", "might", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJR", "IN", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 216, "answer": "Yes, definitely.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "definitely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 235, "question": "You didn't make it easy, did you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "did", "n't", "make", "it", "easy", ",", "did", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "JJ", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 236, "answer": "No, I didn't.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "did", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 251, "question": "Well, what made you fall in love with him?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "what", "made", "you", "fall", "in", "love", "with", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 252, "answer": "I would say Will came at a time in my life where he saw beauty in me that I didn't see in myself at the time.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "say", "Will", "came", "at", "a", "time", "in", "my", "life", "where", "he", "saw", "beauty", "in", "me", "that", "I", "did", "n't", "see", "in", "myself", "at", "the", "time", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 262, "question": "Is that true?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "true", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 263, "answer": "I mean, we make love in some interesting places.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "we", "make", "love", "in", "some", "interesting", "places", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "CD", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 275, "question": "Is that a fault?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "a", "fault", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 276, "answer": "It can be at times but it's not like a crushing fault, but you said, one thing and I gave you one.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "can", "be", "at", "times", "but", "it", "'s", "not", "like", "a", "crushing", "fault", ",", "but", "you", "said", ",", "one", "thing", "and", "I", "gave", "you", "one", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 278, "question": "Do you ever scream at each other?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "ever", "scream", "at", "each", "other", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 279, "answer": "MITH: No, we don't scream at each other.", "answer_tokens": ["MITH", ":", "No", ",", "we", "do", "n't", "scream", "at", "each", "other", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 292, "question": "Who's the boss?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "'s", "the", "boss", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 293, "answer": "Both of us.", "answer_tokens": ["Both", "of", "us", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "RP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 315, "question": "Do you ever get concerned about having kids go down your route so young?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "ever", "get", "concerned", "about", "having", "kids", "go", "down", "your", "route", "so", "young", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "VBG", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 316, "answer": "It's interesting because when I think about the pressures that I had growing up, you know, living in a drug infested neighborhood.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "interesting", "because", "when", "I", "think", "about", "the", "pressures", "that", "I", "had", "growing", "up", ",", "you", "know", ",", "living", "in", "a", "drug", "infested", "neighborhood", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 323, "question": "And when I see these young people, we often get criticized for encouraging them to be stars, but when you hear a Jackie Evancho or someone who is so incredibly gifted, and my first question is, show me the parents?", "question_tokens": ["And", "when", "I", "see", "these", "young", "people", ",", "we", "often", "get", "criticized", "for", "encouraging", "them", "to", "be", "stars", ",", "but", "when", "you", "hear", "a", "Jackie", "Evancho", "or", "someone", "who", "is", "so", "incredibly", "gifted", ",", "and", "my", "first", "question", "is", ",", "show", "me", "the", "parents", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "NNS", ",", "CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "VBN", ",", "CC", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "NN", "PRP", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 324, "answer": "Right.", "answer_tokens": ["Right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jackie Evancho"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 346, "question": "Are you?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 347, "answer": "Yes, I really do.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "really", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 354, "question": "Does it help because you look 25?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "it", "help", "because", "you", "look", "25", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 355, "answer": "Well, thank you.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "thank", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 366, "question": "What's the thing you'd be proudest of, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "the", "thing", "you", "'d", "be", "proudest", "of", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "IN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 367, "answer": "MITH: I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["MITH", ":", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "TO", "VB", "JJS", "IN", "PRP", ",", "NN", ",", "IN", "POS", "RB", "RB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 410, "question": "But why have you become such a popular adviser, guru, relationship adviser?", "question_tokens": ["But", "why", "have", "you", "become", "such", "a", "popular", "adviser", ",", "guru", ",", "relationship", "adviser", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NN", ",", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 411, "answer": "Well, to be honest with you, man, that's really not what I am, you know.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "to", "be", "honest", "with", "you", ",", "man", ",", "that", "'s", "really", "not", "what", "I", "am", ",", "you", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "VBN", "RP", "RB", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "CC", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 435, "question": "What are the principles of manhood?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "the", "principles", "of", "manhood", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 436, "answer": "Well, first of all, it's not what is being put out there today in our music and our videos.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "it", "'s", "not", "what", "is", "being", "put", "out", "there", "today", "in", "our", "music", "and", "our", "videos", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["98 percent"]}, "docId": "110617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "RP", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", ",", "CD", "TO", "CD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "NN", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 449, "question": "ORGAN: Is your mentoring program aimed primarily at young black men or is it wider than that?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "Is", "your", "mentoring", "program", "aimed", "primarily", "at", "young", "black", "men", "or", "is", "it", "wider", "than", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 450, "answer": "Well, it was set up to be wider than that, but because I promote it on my radio show, 97 to 98 percent of the kids that end up at the program are African-American.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "was", "set", "up", "to", "be", "wider", "than", "that", ",", "but", "because", "I", "promote", "it", "on", "my", "radio", "show", ",", "97", "to", "98", "percent", "of", "the", "kids", "that", "end", "up", "at", "the", "program", "are", "African-American", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 452, "question": "And if so, what is it?", "question_tokens": ["And", "if", "so", ",", "what", "is", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "RB", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 453, "answer": "I mean, absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 482, "question": "What values did he give you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "values", "did", "he", "give", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NNS", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 483, "answer": "He taught me hard work.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "taught", "me", "hard", "work", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 491, "question": "What would he have made of what you have made of yourself?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "he", "have", "made", "of", "what", "you", "have", "made", "of", "yourself", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 492, "answer": "Well, I think my father would be proud of me right now, you know.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "my", "father", "would", "be", "proud", "of", "me", "right", "now", ",", "you", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "DT", "RB", "RBR", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "NN", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 494, "question": "What would he have scolded you for?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "he", "have", "scolded", "you", "for", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 495, "answer": "You know, I think a couple relationships he would have wanted me to get it together a little sooner, because my mother and father was married for 64 years.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "think", "a", "couple", "relationships", "he", "would", "have", "wanted", "me", "to", "get", "it", "together", "a", "little", "sooner", ",", "because", "my", "mother", "and", "father", "was", "married", "for", "64", "years", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", ",", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 507, "question": "What would you say to yourself?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "you", "say", "to", "yourself", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 508, "answer": "It's kind of OK, because what I've learned about mistakes and failures is that they're not just complete wipeouts.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "kind", "of", "OK", ",", "because", "what", "I", "'ve", "learned", "about", "mistakes", "and", "failures", "is", "that", "they", "'re", "not", "just", "complete", "wipeouts", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "IN", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 528, "question": "You played that one?", "question_tokens": ["You", "played", "that", "one", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 529, "answer": "I know that you didn't want to have the bad stuff, but that was a nice line.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "know", "that", "you", "did", "n't", "want", "to", "have", "the", "bad", "stuff", ",", "but", "that", "was", "a", "nice", "line", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 537, "question": "If you had your time again in that relationship, what would you do differently to try to stop that from happening?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "had", "your", "time", "again", "in", "that", "relationship", ",", "what", "would", "you", "do", "differently", "to", "try", "to", "stop", "that", "from", "happening", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 538, "answer": "I don't know that I could because I just think, you know, it was at a bad time for me.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "that", "I", "could", "because", "I", "just", "think", ",", "you", "know", ",", "it", "was", "at", "a", "bad", "time", "for", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 563, "question": "Is that how you see it?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "how", "you", "see", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 564, "answer": "I mean, exactly, man.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "exactly", ",", "man", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 568, "question": "Do you think that you're now married for life?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "that", "you", "'re", "now", "married", "for", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 569, "answer": "Oh, yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 571, "question": "Do you believe inside you this is it?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "believe", "inside", "you", "this", "is", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "PRP", "DT", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 572, "answer": "Definitely.", "answer_tokens": ["Definitely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 576, "question": "What was it, do you think, you were really look for in a woman?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "it", ",", "do", "you", "think", ",", "you", "were", "really", "look", "for", "in", "a", "woman", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 577, "answer": "What I have now.", "answer_tokens": ["What", "I", "have", "now", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "RP", "WP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 578, "question": "Which is what?", "question_tokens": ["Which", "is", "what", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "VBZ", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 579, "answer": "I have a woman who wakes up who's completely happy with herself.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "a", "woman", "who", "wakes", "up", "who", "'s", "completely", "happy", "with", "herself", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 595, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 596, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "JJR", "."], "qSentId": 609, "question": "Then why are my husband and my pool man looking for his and his bathroom towels?", "question_tokens": ["Then", "why", "are", "my", "husband", "and", "my", "pool", "man", "looking", "for", "his", "and", "his", "bathroom", "towels", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 610, "answer": "You know, could have been worse.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "could", "have", "been", "worse", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "VB", ",", "RB", "IN", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 618, "question": "Tell me, in all your kind of studies for these books and things, is your conclusion that interracial relationships, marriages, should be encouraged or not encouraged?", "question_tokens": ["Tell", "me", ",", "in", "all", "your", "kind", "of", "studies", "for", "these", "books", "and", "things", ",", "is", "your", "conclusion", "that", "interracial", "relationships", ",", "marriages", ",", "should", "be", "encouraged", "or", "not", "encouraged", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ",", "IN", "DT", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "WDT", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "NNS", ",", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "CC", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 619, "answer": "Well, I mean, for my take on everything, I think people should find love, whatever that is.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "for", "my", "take", "on", "everything", ",", "I", "think", "people", "should", "find", "love", ",", "whatever", "that", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "VBP", ":", "EX", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 641, "question": "As a member of the male species, why the hell would you tell women what we really mean?", "question_tokens": ["As", "a", "member", "of", "the", "male", "species", ",", "why", "the", "hell", "would", "you", "tell", "women", "what", "we", "really", "mean", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", "WP", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 642, "answer": "Because, see -- there's nothing in it for you.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", ",", "see", "--", "there", "'s", "nothing", "in", "it", "for", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 651, "question": "Scented candles?", "question_tokens": ["Scented", "candles", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 652, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "."], "qSentId": 654, "question": "Reading about love and relationships?", "question_tokens": ["Reading", "about", "love", "and", "relationships", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "IN", "JJ", "CC", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 655, "answer": "You.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 674, "question": "Do you?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 675, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]